var Questions = { "question" : [
    {
      "question"  : "What is the meaning of CORPULENT",
       "choice1"  : "Lean",
       "choice2"  : " Gaunt",
       "choice3"  : "Emaciated",
       "choice4"  : "Obese",                   
       "correct"  : 4
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : "pick out the most effective word(s) from the given words.Fate smiles ...... those who untiringly grapple with stark realities of life. ",
       "choice1"  : "with",
       "choice2"  : "over",
       "choice3"  : "on",
       "choice4"  : " round",
       "correct"  : 3
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : "The miser gazed ...... at the pile of gold coins in front of him.",
       "choice1"  : "avidly",
       "choice2"  : "admiringly",
       "choice3"  : "thoughtfully",
       "choice4"  : "earnestly",                    
       "correct"  : 1
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : "Join these parts to make a meaningful sentence.
      1. I

     2. immediately

     3 . salary

     4. my

    5. want ",
       "choice1"  : "43152",
       "choice2"  : "15432",
       "choice3"  : "25143",
       "choice4"  : "42351",                   
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : "1.do
2. today
3. you
4. must
5. it",
       "choice1"  : "34152",
       "choice2"  : "25413",
       "choice3"  : "12543",
       "choice4"  : "51324",               
       "correct"  : 1
    },
    {
      "question"  : "The antonym for ENORMOUS",
       "choice1"  : " Soft",
       "choice2"  : "Average",
       "choice3"  : "Tiny",
       "choice4"  : "Weak",               
       "correct"  :3
    },
    {
      "question"  : "The antonym for COMMISSIONED",
       "choice1"  : "Started",
       "choice2"  : "Closed",
       "choice3"  : "Finished",
       "choice4"  : "Terminated",               
       "correct"  : 4
    },
    {
      "question"  : "Find the correctly spelt word.",
       "choice1"  : "Efficient",
       "choice2"  : "Treatmeant",
       "choice3"  : "Beterment",
       "choice4"  : "Employd",               
       "correct"  : 1
    },
     {
      "question"  : "Find the correctly spelt word.",
       "choice1"  : "Foreign ",
       "choice2"  : "Foreine",
       "choice3"  : "Fariegn",
       "choice4"  : "Forein",               
       "correct"  :1
    },
    {
      "question"  : "Find the correctly spelt word.",
       "choice1"  : "Ommineous",
       "choice2"  : "Omineous",
       "choice3"  : "Ominous",
       "choice4"  : "Omenous",               
       "correct"  : 3
    }
  ]};